sessions.edu 2010-11-11

# Privacy Policy - Sessions College for Professional Design

Sessions College for Professional Design values the privacy of our students, prospective students and all other users of our sites. We diligently safeguard all data collected through our web properties. By using this website, or any other web property operated by Sessions College, you agree to be bound by the policies disclosed herein.

## Audience

This site is intended for the exclusive use of users over the age of 13. Sessions College makes no attempt to track any personally identifiable information from any user under the age of 13. We encourage users under the age of 13 to NOT submit any information to us without the consent and supervision of a legal parent or guardian. 

Visitors outside of the United States should not submit any data unless you agree to be bound by the laws of the United States, rather than by those of your home country.

## Privacy

Sessions College does contact users with information about our curriculum including classes, certificates and degrees. Sessions College actively seeks to preserve the privacy of our users by safeguarding all data collected. Appropriate physical, electronic and managerial safeguards are in place to prevent unauthorized access to all data collected, either actively or passively. While we cannot contractually guarantee the safeguarding of your data, we have taken and will continue to pursue all reasonable measures to ensure your privacy.   Sessions College does not share or rent the contact information or personal data of our users with affiliates or third parties.  Users that elect to subscribe to our sister publication NoD: Notes on Design may occasionally receive email on behalf of the sponsors of Notes on Design.

## Information Collected

Visiting our website will automatically create a record of your visit, which by default consists only data which is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable. You have the choice to identify yourself to us. Data we collect on users who remain anonymous is used primarily to create aggregate user statistics to allow us to better serve our users and tailor content and services. Examples of anonymous access information collected by our sites include, but are not limited to: internet protocol address, browser user agent, referring page, page requested and date and time.

Should you choose to identify yourself to us by any means, including email, telephone, web form submission, online chat, etc., we may associate all data from current and/or previous web sessions, which were previously anonymous, with the data you voluntarily provide in your inquiry. We use the data you actively submit, as well as the data passively collected, for the purposes of responding to your inquiry as well as for internal functions such as marketing analysis or ongoing admissions efforts. 

## Cookies

Our website sets several "cookies" if your browser is configured to accept them. These cookies are required for many functions of our website to work properly. The majority of the cookies set by Sessions College websites are first party cookies, only able to be accessed by web servers at the sessions.edu domain. These cookies are used for features which include, but are not limited to: Dynamic navigation, form submissions, student applications, student registrations, student logins, user analytics, user tracking, live chat, etc. 

Cookies set by any site on the sessions.edu domain are generally first party cookies (meaning that ONLY sessions.edu servers are able to view the contents within) with exceptions for third party services, such as live chat or partner advertisers. In the example of live chat services provided to Sessions by BoldSoftware, Sessions is unable to view or set the contents of these cookies. Conversely, BoldSoftware is unable to view the contents of cookies which Sessions directly sets.

## Use of Personal Information

By submitting personally identifiable information to us, you grant us your consent to contact you by any means you've provided us.

If you no longer wish to be contacted by us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, calling us at the above telephone number, writing to us at the above address. In the case of electronic mail, you may reply or request removal using the link provided within the message

If you enroll in any of our programs or courses, we will honor your request to cease marketing e-mails, however, you cannot unsubscribe from service related emails and notifications. Examples of service notifications include, but are not limited to: Course access instructions, enrollment documents, service outage announcements or any other messages deemed necessary to communicate important information about the program in which you have or were enrolled in. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information (including proprietary information) that we maintain about them.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated policy, we encourage you to contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

### Sessions College

Our postal address is 

398 S. Mill Avenue, Suite 300  
Tempe, AZ 85281

We can be reached via e-mail at info@sessions.edu  
or you can reach us by telephone at 480 -212-1704
